1mpics.com 2015-03-14

# Privacy policy | 1mpics.com

Million Pictures website is founded on the principle of helping People Explore new world photos and photographers.

**We know that you care about how your personal information is used and shared** ,

And we take your privacy very seriously. By visiting the 1mpics website, You are accepting the practices outlined in this policy

  **We collect information to make 1mpics website useful for you.**

Information Collected by 1mpics We only collect personal information that is relevant to the purpose of our website. This information allows us to provide you with a customized and efficient experience. We collect the following types of information from our 1mpics users.

  **We collect your registration and user profile data.** Our servers also collect log information used to make the website faster and better.

**Information You Provide to Us:**

We receive and store any information you enter on our website or provide to us in any other way. You can choose not to provide us with certain information, but then you may not be able to take advantage of many of our special features.

**Registration** : In order for you to use 1mpics services you must complete a registration form. As part of this registration form, we require select personal information.

**User Profile** : To allow you to express yourself beyond just the information collected during registration; we enable you to provide additional information, such as a bio, favorite URLs, and instant messaging IDs. In addition, you may choose to include photos of yourself in your profile. As indicated below, in the section titled "Sharing Your Information", you can control how your information is displayed and used.

**Automatic Information:**

We receive and store certain types of information whenever you interact with us. 1mpics and its authorized agents automatically receive and record certain "traffic data" on their server logs from your browser including your IP address, 1mpics cookie information, and the page you requested. 1mpics uses this traffic data to help diagnose problems with its servers, analyze trends and administer the website.

1mpics may collect and, on any page, display the total counts that page has been viewed. This includes User Profile pages.

  **We will send you emails** based on your profile settings. From time to time, we may send emails to 

all our users

.  
**E-mail Communications**

1mpics is very concerned about your privacy and we will never provide your email address to a third party without your explicit permission, as detailed in the "Sharing Your Information" section below. 1mpics may send out e-mails with 1mpics-related news, products, and offers. You may also receive notification e-mails from 1mpics, which inform you of actions (e.g. new message inbox) that have been sent on the site.

However, please note that in all cases you will continue to receive all system e-mails (e.g. those regarding forgotten user passwords) and legal notices (e.g. updates to our policies) from us.

  **To remember you, our system will give you a cookie. It's safe.**

Cookies are alphanumeric identifiers that we transfer to your computer's hard drive through your Web browser to enable our systems to recognize your browser and tell us how and when pages in our website are visited and by how many people. 1mpics cookies do not collect personal information, and we do not combine information collected through cookies with other personal information to tell us who you are or what your screen name or e-mail address is.

The "help" portion of the toolbar on the majority of browsers will direct you on how to prevent your browser from accepting new cookies, how to command the browser to tell you when you receive a new cookie, or how to fully disable cookies. We recommend that you leave the cookies activated because cookies allow you to use some of 1mpics's coolest features. Some of our business partners, like our advertisers, may use cookies on our website. We have no access to, or control over, these cookies.

  We do not sell your information to anyone. However, we will show publicly available information to other users and may release other information to authorities where required by law.

  Sharing Your Information, because 1mpics enables people to discover and share information with one another, information about the people who use 1mpics is an integral part of the 1mpics experience. Rest assured that we neither rent nor sell your personal information to anyone and that we will share your personal information only as described below.

1mpics Personnel: 1mpics personnel and authorized consultants and/or contractors may have access to user information if necessary in the normal course of 1mpics business.

Protection of 1mpics and Others: We may release personal information when we believe in good faith that release is necessary to comply with a law; to enforce or apply our Terms of Use and other policies; or to protect the rights, property, or safety of 1mpics, our employees, our users, or others. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organizations for fraud protection and credit risk reduction.

User Profile information: Information collected during registration and subsequent visits, such as your full name and location, may be displayed to other 1mpics users in your User Profile. The User Profile is the area on 1mpics where we allow you to tell other 1mpics users about yourself. You may control what personal information is displayed in your User Profile by visiting the Settings section of your User Profile.

Followers' Activity: Much like other online social networks, 1mpics allows non-followers to browse your follower’s activity.

With Your Consent: Except as noted above, we will contact you when your personal information is shared with third parties or used for a purpose incompatible with the purpose(s) for which it was originally collected, and you will be able to opt out to prevent the sharing of this information.

    Your account is protected by an encrypted password. We keep it secure; you must also keep it safe.  
Keeping Information Secure Your 1mpics account information is protected by a password for your privacy and security. Protect against unauthorized access to your password and to your computer by logging off once you have finished using a shared computer.

    **You can choose not to share information with us, but your experience of the site may be limited**.

As stated previously, you can always  not to disclose information, but then you may be unable to use certain features on our website.

**By visiting your User Profile** , you can correct, amend, add or delete personal information on our website.

However, please note that you will continue to receive all system e-mails (e.g. those regarding forgotten user passwords) and legal notices (e.g. updates to our policies) from us.

**As explained earlie** r, the "help" portion of the toolbar on the majority of browsers will direct you on how to prevent your browser from accepting new cookies, how to command the browser to tell you when you receive a new cookie, or how to fully disable cookies. Please note, however, that if your browser does not accept cookies, you will not be able to take advantage of some of our attractive features.

  Advertising

  **Ads appearing on our site** may be delivered to Users by advertising partners, who may set cookies. These cookies allow the ad server to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement to compile non personal identification information about you or others who use your computer. This information allows ad networks to, among other things, deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. This privacy policy does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers.

**Google Adsense**

Some of the ads may be served by Google. Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to Users based on their visit to our Site and other sites on the Internet. DART uses “non personally identifiable information” and does NOT track personal information about you, such as your name, email address, physical address, etc. You may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html

**Compliance with children’s online privacy protection act**

protecting the privacy of the very young is especially important. For that reason, we never collect or maintain information at our Site from those we actually know are under 13, and no part of our website is structured to attract anyone under 13.

  **Privacy policy may change.**

1mpics may amend this Privacy Policy from time to time, at its sole discretion. Use of information we collect now is subject to the Privacy Policy in effect at the time such information is used. If we make changes to the Privacy Policy, we will notify you by posting an announcement on the 1mpics website so you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances if any, it is disclosed.

                                              **Visiting 1mpics is subject to Terms and Privacy policy.**

If you decide to visit 1mpics website, your visit and any possible dispute over privacy is subject to this Privacy Policy and our Terms of Use.
